import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const colors: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What color is \"aka\"?",
    "options": [
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Green",
      "Yellow"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Red",
    "colorOptions": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is \"ao\"?",
    "options": [
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Black",
      "White"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Blue",
    "colorOptions": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is \"shiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "White",
      "Black",
      "Green",
      "Blue"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "White",
    "colorOptions": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is \"kuro\"?",
    "options": [
      "Black",
      "White",
      "Blue",
      "Red"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Black",
    "colorOptions": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is \"midori\"?",
    "options": [
      "Green",
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Yellow"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Green",
    "colorOptions": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"red\"?",
    "options": [
      "ao",
      "aka",
      "shiro",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aka",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"white\"?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "shiro",
      "kuro",
      "midori"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"blue\"?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "midori",
      "ao",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ao",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"green\"?",
    "options": [
      "kuro",
      "midori",
      "aka",
      "shiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "midori",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"black\"?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "kuro",
      "aka",
      "ao"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kuro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"aka\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "あか",
      "あお",
      "しろ",
      "みどり"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "あか",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"shiro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "くろ",
      "しろ",
      "あか",
      "あお"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "しろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"ao\"?",
    "options": [
      "アオ",
      "アカ",
      "クロ",
      "ミドリ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "アオ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"kuro\"?",
    "options": [
      "白",
      "青",
      "黒",
      "赤"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "黒",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"shiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "白",
      "赤",
      "青",
      "黒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "白",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the sky?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "ao",
      "midori",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ao",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of blood?",
    "options": [
      "midori",
      "aka",
      "shiro",
      "ao"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aka",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which word means \"green\" in Japanese?",
    "options": [
      "midori",
      "ao",
      "aka",
      "shiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "midori",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What color do you get if you mix \"aka\" and \"ao\"?",
    "options": [
      "murasaki",
      "shiro",
      "aka",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "murasaki",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color red?",
    "options": [
      "赤",
      "白",
      "青",
      "黒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "赤",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"midori\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "みどり",
      "ぴんく",
      "おれんじ",
      "くろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "みどり",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"kuro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "くろ",
      "ぴんく",
      "あお",
      "みどり"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "くろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"haiiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "灰",
      "黄",
      "緑",
      "黒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "灰",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"ao\"?",
    "options": [
      "青",
      "緑",
      "桃",
      "黒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "青",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What color do you get if you mix \"aka\" and \"ao\"?",
    "options": [
      "murasaki",
      "shiro",
      "aka",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "murasaki",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the night sky?",
    "options": [
      "kuro",
      "aka",
      "shiro",
      "orenji"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kuro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"haiiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "ハイイロ",
      "オレンジ",
      "ムラサキ",
      "キイロ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ハイイロ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the sun?",
    "options": [
      "kiiro",
      "ao",
      "midori",
      "pinku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kiiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"shiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "白",
      "赤",
      "黄",
      "紫"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "白",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"pinku\"?",
    "options": [
      "ピンク",
      "オレンジ",
      "ハイイロ",
      "キイロ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ピンク",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the ocean?",
    "options": [
      "ao",
      "aka",
      "kiiro",
      "chairo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ao",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of ash?",
    "options": [
      "haiiro",
      "midori",
      "chairo",
      "murasaki"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "haiiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of chocolate?",
    "options": [
      "chairo",
      "ao",
      "aka",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chairo",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a pink flower?",
    "options": [
      "pinku",
      "haiiro",
      "murasaki",
      "chairo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pinku",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"orenji\"?",
    "options": [
      "オレンジ",
      "ピンク",
      "ハイイロ",
      "チャイロ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "オレンジ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a strawberry?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "haiiro",
      "pinku",
      "midori"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aka",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"haiiro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "はいいろ",
      "あか",
      "しろ",
      "くろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "はいいろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"orenji\"?",
    "options": [
      "橙",
      "白",
      "赤",
      "黒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "橙",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"aka\"?",
    "options": [
      "赤",
      "桃",
      "白",
      "黒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "赤",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What color do you get if you mix \"ao\" and \"midori\"?",
    "options": [
      "aomidori",
      "kiiro",
      "murasaki",
      "aka"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aomidori",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"murasaki\"?",
    "options": [
      "紫",
      "茶",
      "黒",
      "白"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "紫",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of cotton?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "midori",
      "kiiro",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"kiiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "黄",
      "青",
      "桃",
      "緑"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "黄",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"orenji\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "おれんじ",
      "あか",
      "きいろ",
      "しろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "おれんじ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of grass?",
    "options": [
      "midori",
      "kiiro",
      "haiiro",
      "ao"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "midori",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"chairo\"?",
    "options": [
      "チャイロ",
      "ピンク",
      "キイロ",
      "オレンジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チャイロ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"chairo\"?",
    "options": [
      "茶",
      "青",
      "紫",
      "黒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "茶",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"murasaki\"?",
    "options": [
      "ムラサキ",
      "ハイイロ",
      "オレンジ",
      "チャイロ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ムラサキ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a banana?",
    "options": [
      "kiiro",
      "orenji",
      "ao",
      "aka"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kiiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"pinku\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ぴんく",
      "あお",
      "あか",
      "はいいろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぴんく",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of snow?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "murasaki",
      "orenji",
      "pinku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"kuro\"?",
    "options": [
      "黒",
      "灰",
      "紫",
      "黄"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "黒",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"shiro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "しろ",
      "ちゃいろ",
      "むらさき",
      "くろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "しろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"midori\"?",
    "options": [
      "緑",
      "黄",
      "青",
      "橙"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "緑",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a cloud?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "pinku",
      "ao",
      "murasaki"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"ao\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "あお",
      "おれんじ",
      "みどり",
      "ちゃいろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "あお",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"kiiro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "きいろ",
      "くろ",
      "ぴんく",
      "あお"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "きいろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of coal?",
    "options": [
      "kuro",
      "kiiro",
      "chairo",
      "midori"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kuro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"aka\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "あか",
      "むらさき",
      "あお",
      "ぴんく"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "あか",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of an eggplant?",
    "options": [
      "murasaki",
      "kuro",
      "haiiro",
      "aka"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "murasaki",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Kanji represents the color \"pinku\"?",
    "options": [
      "桃",
      "橙",
      "黒",
      "茶"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "桃",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"murasaki\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "むらさき",
      "くろ",
      "あか",
      "みどり"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "むらさき",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What color do you get if you mix \"aka\" and \"midori\"?",
    "options": [
      "orenji",
      "chairo",
      "haiiro",
      "kiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "orenji",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of an orange fruit?",
    "options": [
      "orenji",
      "haiiro",
      "ao",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "orenji",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a rose?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "ao",
      "midori",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aka",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"kiiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "キイロ",
      "ハイイロ",
      "ピンク",
      "ムラサキ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "キイロ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"chairo\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ちゃいろ",
      "しろ",
      "むらさき",
      "あか"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ちゃいろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a sunflower?",
    "options": [
      "kiiro",
      "chairo",
      "haiiro",
      "pinku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kiiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What color represents 'go' on a traffic light?",
    "options": [
      "midori",
      "shiro",
      "ao",
      "pinku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "midori",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a sky?",
    "options": [
      "ao",
      "murasaki",
      "orenji",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ao",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a lemon?",
    "options": [
      "kiiro",
      "haiiro",
      "shiro",
      "murasaki"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kiiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"haiiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "ハイイロ",
      "ピンク",
      "オレンジ",
      "ムラサキ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ハイイロ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"kiiro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "きいろ",
      "あか",
      "はいいろ",
      "みどり"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "きいろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a rust?",
    "options": [
      "chairo",
      "pinku",
      "shiro",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chairo",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a blood?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "chairo",
      "kiiro",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aka",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"pinku\"?",
    "options": [
      "ピンク",
      "キイロ",
      "ムラサキ",
      "ハイイロ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ピンク",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"midori\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "みどり",
      "むらさき",
      "ぴんく",
      "はいいろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "みどり",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"haiiro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "はいいろ",
      "あお",
      "ちゃいろ",
      "しろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "はいいろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"murasaki\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "むらさき",
      "はいいろ",
      "おれんじ",
      "くろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "むらさき",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a chalkboard?",
    "options": [
      "midori",
      "ao",
      "orenji",
      "murasaki"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "midori",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"chairo\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ちゃいろ",
      "くろ",
      "あお",
      "きいろ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ちゃいろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a orange?",
    "options": [
      "orenji",
      "chairo",
      "haiiro",
      "kiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "orenji",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a traffic light (stop)?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "shiro",
      "orenji",
      "ao"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aka",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a chalk?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "pinku",
      "haiiro",
      "kiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"pinku\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ぴんく",
      "みどり",
      "きいろ",
      "あお"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぴんく",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a rose?",
    "options": [
      "pinku",
      "orenji",
      "murasaki",
      "aka"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pinku",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"kiiro\"?",
    "options": [
      "キイロ",
      "ムラサキ",
      "チャイロ",
      "オレンジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "キイロ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"shiro\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "しろ",
      "くろ",
      "むらさき",
      "みどり"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "しろ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"chairo\"?",
    "options": [
      "チャイロ",
      "ピンク",
      "ムラサキ",
      "オレンジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チャイロ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"aka\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "あか",
      "みどり",
      "きいろ",
      "あお"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "あか",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a ash?",
    "options": [
      "haiiro",
      "shiro",
      "pinku",
      "aka"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "haiiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a shadow?",
    "options": [
      "kuro",
      "haiiro",
      "midori",
      "aka"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kuro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a milk?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "kuro",
      "pinku",
      "midori"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a coal?",
    "options": [
      "kuro",
      "pinku",
      "murasaki",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kuro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a mud?",
    "options": [
      "chairo",
      "murasaki",
      "shiro",
      "kiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chairo",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a firetruck?",
    "options": [
      "aka",
      "midori",
      "shiro",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aka",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a ice?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "chairo",
      "orenji",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is the Katakana for \"murasaki\"?",
    "options": [
      "ムラサキ",
      "ハイイロ",
      "キイロ",
      "オレンジ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ムラサキ",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a grass?",
    "options": [
      "midori",
      "ao",
      "murasaki",
      "haiiro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "midori",
    "colorOptions": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of a panda?",
    "options": [
      "shiro",
      "chairo",
      "murasaki",
      "kuro"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shiro",
    "colorOptions": false
  }
];

export default colors;
